[Music]
[Música]
I have to catch up on that [ __ ]
me tengo que poner al día con esa movida
man it's that I'm here today
tío es que estoy hoy se terminado el
Daniel Sancho's trial is over now now
juicio de Daniel Sancho ahora ahora
when I'm done with you guys I'm going to, I'm going to
cuando termine con ustedes voy a voy a
record a video for the main channel, I'm
grabar un vídeo para el canal principal
probably going to record a
seguramente voy a grabar seguramente un
video for the main channel to give
vídeo para el canal principal para darle
some closure. Well, more than closure, a
un cierre a Bueno más que un cierre un
seen for sentencing, no, and from
visto para sentencia no y de
there and from there
ahí y de ahí
I'll record the two newscasts and I have to
me grabaré los dos noticieros y me tengo
catch up on that man, with that
que poner al día con eso tío con ese
topic. Well, let's see this Case, no longer
tema Bueno vamos a ver esto Case ya no
how much of the day that you're
cuanto de día que esto me lo estáis
sending me this and I haven't commented on it either,
mandando y no lo he comentado tampoco
okay, the thing about Karches, yes, we did
vale lo del tema de karches sí que lo sí
see it,
que lo vimos sí que mencionamos algo lo
yes, we mentioned something, what I don't remember is if we mentioned it in a newscast or in a live show, okay, but apparently there's been more, apparently there's been more and on top of that Karches' mother, I don't know if Nauter brings it up in the video, doesn't bring it up
lo saca en el vídeo no lo saca la madre
in the video. Well, let's see it and what
en el vídeo Bueno pues vamos a verlo y y
if Nauter doesn't bring it up in the video,
si no lo saca nauter en el vídeo lo lo
we'll add it because Karimi was fighting
añadimos nosotros pu se estuvo peleando
with the mother and I was all  the
karimi con la madre y me estaba todo el
world sending me Elo and I [ __ ] but
mundo mandándome Elo y yo [__] pero
since we haven't done a live stream we've
como no hemos hecho directo hemos
commented Carche's mother got into an argument
comentado la madre de carche se peleó
with Karime dude the other day on Twitter about
con Karime chaval el otro día en Twitter
the controversial clip of Karches talking about
el polémico clip de karches hablando de
when Auron Play called the people
cuando auron Play dijo ratas a la gente
who were supporting the funa against
que estuvo apoyando la funa en contra de
him rats okay Okay until Ao doesn't feel like it
él vale Vale hasta que a ao no le de la
I'm going to continue with that
gana de eso yo voy a seguir con esa
image for life okay let's see it
imagen de por vida okay vamos a verlo
one day in a streaming you come and
que un día en un streaming vienes y me
hit me twice and he tells me if you're a G I'll
pegas dos puñetas y me dice si eres un G
go and it goes viral
yo me pongo y se viraliza
no from there on do whatever you do no
no partir de ahí hagas lo que hagas no
but we saw the clienterror
pero vimos el clienterror
weren't they basically chatting about
no estaban Charlando básicamente sobre
how to take the funas no and the criticism
Cómo tomarse las funas no y las críticas
on the internet yes put it up no put
en internet si soportarlas no
it up yes look the other way no
soportarlas si mirar hacia otro lado no
and take things from whoever it comes from it
y tomarte las cosas de quien viene est
's like always Ah but this was the one that I do
es como siempre Ah pero este fue el que
n't know what but and only and many
no sé qué pero y solamente y muchas
times there's only one way for that to
veces solamente hay una manera de que
happen is if there are several
eso de que eso pase es si hay varias
people involved that those people
personas involucradas que esas personas
all agree to say this
se pongan todas de acuerdo en decir esto
is not the case and insist and say this is not the
no es así y insistir y decir esto no es
case until  that narrative is removed,
así hasta que se quita esa narrativa yo
for example, my thing, the rat thing.
por ejemplo lo mío lo de la rata Yo
Until Auro comes out live tomorrow,
hasta que Auro el día de mañana no salga
hey guys, hey, you
diciendo en directo Oye chavales eh le
call this guy a rat, this guy is
llamáis rata a este tío este tío no es
nothing like this, until Auro feels like
nada de esto hasta que Auro no le dé la
doing that, I'm going to continue with
gana de hacer eso yo voy a seguir con
that image all my life, all my life, for the
esa imagen toda la toda la vida para el
casual public, all my life it's like that. I think
público casual toda la vida es así Creo
that this is also very noticeable on tiktok
que también eso se nota mucho en tiktok
and on other platforms that it's like,
y en otras plataformas que que es como
Oh but this was the one with I don't know what, that's
Ah pero este era el de no sé qué eso
okay, I'll tell you one thing, I'll tell you one thing, I'll tell you
vale os digo una cosa os digo una cosa
one thing,
eh os digo una cosa volviendo la
listening again the other day we didn't
escuchar que el otro día no lo
hear it well, okay, saying live.
escuchamos bien vale diciendo en directo
Hey guys, hey, that narrative is removed,
Oye chavales eh se quite esa narrativa
for example, my thing, the rat thing.
yo por ejemplo lo mío lo de la rata Yo
Until Auron comes out live tomorrow,
hasta que auron el día de mañana no
hey guys,
salga diciendo en directo Oye chavales
hey, you call this guy a rat, this guy
eh le llamáis rata a este tío este tío
is nothing like this, until Auron feels like doing that,
no es nada de esto hasta que auron no le
I'm going to continue
dé la gana de hacer eso yo voy a seguir
with that image all my life, okay. On the one
con esa imagen toda la vale Por una
hand, m On the one hand, I have to tell you
parte m Por una parte tengo que deciros
that, eh  a part to see It is more than
que eh Por una parte a ver Es más que
evident that he is like claiming
evidente que le está como reclamando
Almost almost asking okay it is almost a
Casi casi pidiendo vale casi es una
request to Auron to speak out at
petición a auron que se pronuncie en
some point when he has the pateca okay
algún momento cuando ha la pateca vale
that he speaks out on this subject
que se pronuncie sobre sobre este tema
okay about that he is fine with karches
vale sobre que está bien con karches
okay I mean he is not telling you because of
vale o sea no te está diciendo porque
course the headline of uncle shur that I
claro el titular del tío shur que yo me
found out eh From the headline of uncle shur I don't
enteré eh Por el titular del tío shur no
know if anyone else him or someone put the
sé si alguno más él o alguno puso lo
same thing okay And I don't know if even We
mismo vale Y no sé si incluso Nosotros
were also commenting on it the other
también lo estuvimos comentando el otro
day and I interpreted it the same It is that he
día y lo interpreté igual Es que él
was denying or that karche was
estaba negando o seaa que karche estaba
denying that this story was because of him
negando que esta historia fuera por él
okay let's see for me and I really say this
vale a ver para mí y de verdad lo digo
without any intention of offending carch or
sin sin ánimo de ofender a carch ni
attacking him or anything like that But I
atacarlo ni nada por el estilo Pero yo
am telling you what I think of what Auron
te estoy diciendo lo que pienso de lo
put I think it was because of
que puso auron Yo pienso que fue por
several content creators okay among which
varios creadores de contenido vale entre
was karches why do I
los que se encontraba karches por qué lo
think that Well look, I think it is because
pienso Pues mira pues lo pienso porque
at that time In those days I
en ese momento En aquellos días yo
was very in contact with Auro he didn't
estaba muy en contacto con Auro él no me
tell me either This is about carche or anything like that
dijo tampoco Esto va por carche ni nada
uh I mean I don't want I don't
por el estilo eh o sea no quiero no
want to put words in
quiero poner yo palabras en la boca de
anyone's mouth that haven't already been told to me but it's
nadie tampoco que no me hayan dicho pero
true that I remember this story
sí que es verdad que esta historia me
perfectly and
acuerdo perfectamente que además
we were also live okay uh we were
estábamos en directo vale eh estábamos
live I don't remember what we were
en directo no me acuerdo a Qué estábamos
reacting to exactly but we were
reaccionando exactamente pero estbamos
reacting to this type of things Not to
reaccionando a este tipo de cosas No a
what karche was doing when
lo que karche estaba haciendo cuando
karche gave him the spa auron no how he
karche le dio la espa auron no cómo se
behaved with him I don't know what and auron well he
portó con él no sé qué Y auron pues
was yes he wasn't watching my live streams
estaba si no estaba viendo mis directos
those days he used to watch them a lot in fact
esos días solía verlos muchos De hecho
I had some exclusives things no
yo tuve algunas exclusivas las cosas no
uh Not only to karche Yes I mean I
eh No solamente a karche Eso sí O sea yo
think it goes for several creators among those
pienso que va por varios creadores entre
among those who were karche
los que entre los que iba a karche
involved okay but I think he
involucrado vale pero yo creo que esto
also said this to wismichu and he
se lo dijo también a wismichu y se lo
told him I mean to Felipe maybe I think he
dijo O sea a Felipe a lo mejor yo creo
told it to all of those who were
que se lo dijo a todos los que estaban
taking advantage of the fact that he was on the ground at
Aprovechando que él estaba en el suelo
that moment to uh To step on him
ese momento para eh Para pisarle
Taking advantage of the fact that he was in a
Aprovechando que estaba en un momento
weak moment to hit him okay that's what I
débil para darle vale eso es lo que yo
think if auron comes out and says No no it's not that I didn't  I
pienso a mí si auron sale Y dice No no
put it for nothing, it wouldn't
es que no lo puse por nada no me
seem too false to me on Auron's part.
parecería muy falso por parte de auron
But what I'm hearing here,
Pero lo que yo estoy escuchando aquí
okay, now listening again, maybe he's
vale ahora escuchando de nuevo no es a
telling IB that
lo mejor que le esté diciendo a IB lo de
Auron's thing wasn't because of me, which was the headline I
auron no fue por mí que era el titular
saw the other day, meaning to say this isn't
que vi el otro día es decir esto no es
true and to insist and say this isn't true
así y insistir y decir esto no es así
until that narrative is removed. He's not
hasta que se quite esa narrativa él no
saying that Auron's thing wasn't
está diciendo que lo de auron no fuera
because of him, he's saying that when Auron
por él él está diciendo que cuando auron
comes out and tells his audience that
salga y le diga su audiencia que está
everything is fine with Carche, people might
todo bien con carche pues la gente a lo
leave him. Okay, yes, it's
mejor lo dejará vale que sí que es
true that Auron hasn't said
verdad que auron no ha dicho
absolutely nothing. Auron hasn't said
absolutamente nada auron no ha dicho
absolutely nothing. eh. Look, I'm not going to
absolutamente nada eh A ver yo no voy a
talk about private versions,
hablar con verciones privadas
obviously, but I do have to
evidentemente pero sí que tengo que
tell you that
deciros que
I was very critical of Carche and there
yo era muy crítico con carche y a mí
were two friends in common, two colleagues in
hubo dos amigos en común dos colegas en
common, okay, two colleagues in common, eh, two
común vale dos colegas en común eh dos
colleagues in common of mine with Carche, okay, who
colegas en común mío con carche vale que
get along with me and who get along with
se lleva conmigo y que se llevan con
Carche more or less, okay, and they told me that,
carche más o menos vale y me dijeron que
man, Carche wasn't
hombre que carche que no estaba
managing things well and that he
gestionando bien el he y que que no lo
wasn't having a good time with the criticism.  I don't
estáa pasando bien con las críticas no
know what and I already said look Okay well that's it we've
sé qué y yo ya dije mira Vale pues ya
already said everything that had to be
está ya hemos dicho todo lo que se tenía
said I'm going
que decir voy
to leave it in palla past the subject
a dejarlo en palla pasado el tema
also no but but at the but at time
también no pero al pero al tiempo
also yes that Costa yes that I ca that uh
también sí que me Costa sí que que me ca
that they fixed it okay that they
que eh que lo arreglaron vale que lo
fixed it I mean that they talked yes there
arreglaron o sea que hablaron sí que
was one time when Carch came out with the
hubo una vez que carch salió con la
hamburger saying we haven't
hamburguesa diciendo no lo hemos
fixed it I don't know what he talks to Auron
arreglado no sé qué habla con auron está
everything is fine and it was a lie okay but but
todo bien y era mentira vale pero pero
then a few months ago there was an
luego hace unos meses sí que hubo un
approach Okay now I don't know I don't know the
acercamiento Vale ahora no s no sé el
content of that approach I would have
contenido de ese acercamiento me hubiera
loved for one of the two to tell it
encantado que lo contasen alguno de los
either Karches or Auros the
dos o bien karches o bien auros la
truth because Hey I don't know I would love to
verdad porque Oye no sé me encantaría
know if Carche maintains her position or
saber si carche mantiene su postura o
simply doesn't want to be attacked
simplemente no quiere que la ataquen
But she continues to maintain her position or
Pero sigue manteniendo su postura o o se
has apologized Hey look Auron it's true I
ha disculp Oye mira auron es verdad me
behaved badly I shouldn't have taken a
porté mal no tuve que haberme
position or supported my
posicionado o haber apoyado a mi a mi
girlfriend in this that she was saying you know
novia en esto que estaba diciendo sabes
and have turned my back on you at this
y haberte dado la espalda en este
moment so so low you know So we do
momento tan tan bajo sabes Entonces eso
n't know that I mean I I know and I can
no lo sabemos o sea yo yo sé y os puedo
guarantee you that there has been an  approach
garantizar que ha habido un acercamiento
and that they have talked and that at least
y que han hablado y que por lo menos
each one looks they are at peace and that they
cada uno mira están en paz y que ahí se
have each other there no they do not bother each other no each other
tienen no no se molestan no entre ellos
no eh but it is that Auron made that
no eh pero es que auron tomó esa
determination I think that with everything eh I do
determinación Yo creo que con todo eh yo
not know if Auron got to talk to
no sé si auron llegó a hablar con
wismichu the truth is I do not know if Auron
wismichu la verdad yo no sé si auron
got to talk to Win michu Who
llegó a hablar con Win michu Quiénes
were the ones that I mean the thing was with Win
eran los que o sea el rollo era con Win
michu no that he got involved at most in the
michu no que se metió como mucho en el
subject with cach for the issue of
tema con con cach por el tema de la
betrayal no eh ungrateful And such And with
traición no eh desagradecido Y tal Y con
whom else was Auron having problems
quién más estaba teniendo los problemas
who was putting him like a lot of
auron quién le estaba metiendo como tela
traya man I know that he was in the
de traya hombre Yo sé que estaba en la
nu this one that was like super full throttle not
nu este que estaba como super a tope no
Felipe but Felipe What is Felipe Felipe
el Felipe pero es que Felipe Qué es
What is Felipe different
Felipe Felipe A qué se diferencia Felipe
today from an account like this from
a día de hoy a una cuenta de estas de a
an Abi or something like this on Twitter
una Abi o a una cosa de esta de Twitter
you understand but more or less that it
me entiendes pero así más o menos que
has a certain that it had a certain
tenga cierta que tuviera cierta
repercussion man what happened with Juan also what happened
repercusión hombre lo de Juan también lo
with Juan I would love to know what it had become
de Juan me encantaría saber en qué había
really is that I can find out
quedado a verad es que me puedo enterar
but don't you  I could tell you all the same
pero no os lo podría contar Igualmente
but no, honestly, I'm not
pero no la verdad no me no me ha
interested either, I mean, I've heard that there have
interesado tampoco o sea he sabido que
been conversations, for example, with you
ha habido conversaciones por ejemplo con
saw the Turboplane video and I said to myself,
viste el vídeo de turboplane que me decí
let's watch a Turboplane video. I've got
vamos a ver un vídeo de turboplane llevo
a surprise here, let's see. I know there have
por aquí una sorpresa a ver Sé que ha
been conversations ta ta ta ta No, I haven't
habido conversaciones ta ta ta ta No no
seen this video. Honestly, how are you
lo he visto Este vídeo La verdad qué tal
guys? How angry does it make me that you do that to me?
chicos qué coraje me da que me haga eso
The browser, this wasn't the one in the
el navegador este no fue el de la
complaint, it's not the same one as the Ah No, the one
denuncia no es el mismo de lo Ah No El
in the complaint was this one, well, I haven't
de la denuncia fue este no pues no lo he
seen it, honestly, I haven't seen it, but
visto la verdad no lo he visto pero
anyway, I know that there were
bueno vamos que sé que hubo
conversations with Juan and Ari, there was
conversaciones con Juan y con Ari hubo
a meeting, the four of them, okay. I don't know the
una reunión los cuatro vale No sé el
content, and they also spoke with Carche,
contenido y con carche también hablaron
okay. I don't know if Karche approached me and I don't know
vale No sé si karche se acercó y no sé
if he regretted it or not or not. I do
si se arrepintió o no se arrepintió o no
n't know the truth is that I don't know that they haven't
No sé la verdad es que no sé que no han
given any explanation. Honestly, very
dado ninguna explicación la verdad muy
good, my beloved audience, how are you? Carche is
buenas mi amado público qué tal carche
coming back to the Channel, let's see what he has to
vuelve al Canal veamos que nos tiene que
tell us. I know that, for example, my career,
contar Yo sé que por ejemplo mi carrera
aside from my lack of consistency
al margen de mi falta de de constancia
last year of not doing live shows c days
el año pasado de no hacer directo c días
a week or days a week and the
a la semana o se días a la semana y las
hours that were aside from that I know
horas que fuesen al margen de eso yo sé
that because of him my career has also been
que por el también mi carrera se ha
seen apparently he has been talking to about is that
visto al parecer ha estado hablando con
he says the hate eh that for
de es que él dice el hate eh que por
example they took out the clip of me that
ejemplo a mí me sacaban el clip de que
I said you deserve to lose all the
yo decía te mereces perder todos los
followers and like that let's see if
seguidores y como que yo vamos a ver si
you everything and this happens Okay right now he
tú todo y esto pasa Vale ahora mismo
is also in coi he has ibai has also
también está en coi tiene ibai también
had a growth Maybe with
ha tenido un crecimiento A lo mejor con
his relationship with Abi I don't know okay But
su relación con Abi No lo sé vale Pero
if you let's see for me on the internet for me
si tú a ver para mí en internet para mí
on the internet there are people who have their
en internet hay gente que tiene su
community and who have their audience
comunidad y que tiene su público más
larger or smaller but they have their
grande o más pequeño pero tiene su
audience their people and there are people who have
público su gente y hay gente que tiene
their audience of another, I mean for example there is
su su Público de otro o sea por ejemplo
a youtuber who has his
hay un youtuber que que tiene su
community and then there are youtubers who are
comunidad y luego hay youtubers que son
like friends secondary colleagues
como amigos colegas secundarios canales
secondary channels of that youtuber and they have their
secundarios de ese youtuber y tienen su
community or a part of their community if
comunidad o una parte de su comunidad si
you all one thing is
tú todo lo una cosa son las
collaborations Because for example I have
colaboraciones Porque yo por ejemplo he
collaborated with other youtubers okay And
colaborado con otros youtubers vale Y yo
thanks to me a lot of people have subscribed
gracias a mí se ha suscrito mucha gente
to him and thanks to him a lot of
a él y gracias a él se ha suscrito mucha
people have subscribed to me and we do collaboration
gente a mí y hacemos colaboración
we exchange audience okay
intercambiamos público vale intereses
mutual interests okay but it's  other youtubers
mutuos vale pero está otros youtubers
like me I think it has been for example
como yo creo que ha sido por ejemplo
carch and some who were around
carch y algunos que estaban alrededor de
auron Okay and and the one who has the
auron Vale y y y el que tiene la
community is auron and then yours is
comunidad es auron y luego lo tuyo es de
auron's So if what you have is
auron Entonces si tú lo que tienes es de
auron's if you do something so ugly to
auron si tú le haces una cosa tan fea a
auron of course people leave you without
auron claro la gente es que se te va sin
auron even saying anything okay I've
que auron ni siquiera diga nada vale eso
seen that on other occasions I've
lo he visto yo en otras ocasiones
also seen it happen eh On a
también lo he visto que ha pasado eh A
larger or smaller scale but it has happened it's
mayor a menor escala pero es que ha
that if you in the end if you
pasado es que si tú al final si tú
have a community that depended on someone
tienes una comunidad que dependía de
else Well of course then you can't then you can't you can't
otro Pues claro luego no te puedes luego
complain yes you do
no te puedes no te puedes quejar si lo
lose a lot when you fail
si pierdes mucho cuando tú le fallas a
that person you understand And it's not that it's not that you
esa persona me entiendes Y no es que no
owe them mercy your whole life
es que le debas clemencia toda la vida
but man You have to be grateful in
pero hombre Hay que ser agradecido en
this life and value who has given to you, I mean
esta vida y valorar quién te ha dado o
because for me, what's true is you're
sea porque para mí yo que verad tú me
going to call me old-fashioned or whatever okay
vais a llamar antiguo o lo que sea vale
but I value a lot Who gives me
pero yo valoro mucho Quién me da de
food or who puts a plate in my house
comer o quién pone un plato en mi casa
you know that obviously it's me
sabes que evidentemente soy yo
working but if  a person
trabajando pero si a mí una persona me
has helped me I mean imagine I'm going to
ha ayudado O sea imagínate te voy a
give you an example Fran cuaa I could
poner un ejemplo Fran cuaa yo me podré
fight with Fran someday and I could
pelear con Fran cuesta algún día y podré
discuss a thousand things but I will always
discutir mil cosas pero yo siempre le
have respect for him and I will always
voy a tener un respeto y siempre le voy
be grateful to him because with me and with
a estar agradecido porque conmigo y con
my family he contributed spectacularly Not
mi familia aportado espectacular Ya no
only when I went to Thailand that he
solamente cuando fui a Tailandia que me
gave me his house he gave me everything I didn't lack
dio su casa me dio de todo no me faltaba
anything eh to me and my wife they behaved
De nada eh a mí con mi mujer se portaron
spectacular okay that's it for me I will
espectacular vale son eso para mí eso me
take that with me for the rest of my life but
lo llevo yo para toda la vida sino que
also right here at my job
además aquí mismo en mi trabajo
interviews live debates videos or I mean a
entrevistas debates directos vídeos o
thousand things that whether you like it or not well he
sea mil cosas que eso quieras que no
pays my mortgage it's not in the end I know in the
pues paga mi hipoteca no es al final se
end that translates into host well
al final eso se traduce en [__] pues
[ __ ] it's income for my house you
[__] son ingresos para mi casa me
understand So well one day I'll be
entiendes Entonces pues yo un día me
able to fight, I'll be able to get angry imagine
podré pelear me podré enfadar imagínate
[ __ ] well I don't like Franco anymore this
[__] pues ya no me gusta Franco esta
I'm retiring I'm leaving or but I will
me retiro me alejo o pero yo ese respeto
always have that respect and I can
siempre se lo voy a tener y te puedo
tell you Fran like I can tell you
decir Fran como te puedo decir otras
many other people no I mean for me it's that I
muchas personas no O sea yo para mí es
value because I've spent my
que eso lo valoro porque yo he estado
whole [ __ ] life working in
toda la [__] vida trabajando en trabajo
someone else's job  type you know and that's something here on the
de otro tipo sabes y eso es algo aquí en
internet that kids don't value and And
internet que los chavales no valoran y Y
you collaborate Maybe with someone and you
tú colaboras A lo mejor con alguien y le
give a springboard to someone who
pegas un trampolín a alguien que
more or less manages to get going no or
consigue más o menos impulsarse no o
have that small start Not here where you
tener ese pequeño inicio No aquí que se
need that showcase no that you
necesita ese escaparate no que se
need on YouTube to start and then they
necesita en YouTube para empezar y luego
put the they put the stab in you and it's
te meten la te meten La puñalada y a mí
happened to me uh a lot uh that they've
me ha pasado eh mucho eh que me han
put the stab in me after
metido La puñalada después de que a lo
maybe thanks to or having been by my
mejor gracias a o de haber estado a mi
side they've had the opportunity to be able to
lado han tenido la oportunidad de poder
have Hey maybe he's not rich but
tener Oye a lo mejor no es rico pero a
maybe Hey a salary Hey I'm not telling you that you
lo mejor Oye un sueldo Oye no te digo
owe me homage or that I'm your
que me debas pleitesía o que yo sea tu
God or something like that but at
Dios o alguna cosa de esa pero que
least not stab me you understand at
mínimo que no apuñalarme me entiendes
least not stab me okay And it's
que mínimo que no apuñalarme vale Y me
happened to me many times that I've given
ha pasado muchas veces que le he dado a
people Eh a place and a site no and they
la gente Eh un lugar y un sitio no y te
stab you and it's like you [ __ ] I mean it's like
apuñala y es como ti [__] o sea es como
Look so I can translate it to so you can
Mira para que lo traduzca a a la para
find an analogy
que para que encontréis una analogía
okay real life okay  eh Imagine that
vale la vida real vale eh Imagínate que
you're going through a bad time in your life
tú estás en un mal momento de la vida
you're looking for a job and a friend or a
estás buscando trabajo y un amigo o un
neighbor a neighbor gets you into their company to
vecino un vecino te mete en su empresa a
work and they stand up for you talk to
trabajar y da la cara por ti habla con
your boss and they get you into their company damn Well
tu jefe y te mete en su empresa a
you have to stand up
trabajar [__] Pues tú tienes que dar la
for him not make a deal in that
cara por él no hacer una tratada en esa
company and make the face of the one who got
empresa y que dejes mal la cara de del
you into it those are behaviors they're
del que te ha metido que son conductas
unwritten laws of behavior
son leyes de comportamiento no escritas
you know they're unwritten laws of behavior
sabes son leyes de comportamiento no
so in better or worse way
escrita entonces con mejor o peor forma
because the truth is that
porque la verdad me estaba tocando mucho
his girlfriend at the time was really getting on my nerves
las narices su novia en aquel momento
when her girlfriend called me a [ __ ] and
que me que su novia me llamaba [__] y
said a lot of disgusting things to me
me decía un montón de cosas asquerosas
Abi okay eh Well I think it's
la Abi vale eh que Bueno yo creo que es
more than obvious that if you've
más que evidente que si me habéis
heard me talking about her in the
escuchado hablando sobre ella en los
last few months the tone has changed and the
últimos meses el tono ha cambiado y el
term has changed because [ __ ] she's not
término ha cambiado porque [__] [__] No
messing with me while she's not
se está metiendo conmigo mientras que no
insulting me Well the other guy called me
me falta Bueno me llamó el otro d hace
recently and insulted me But well I'll take it
poco me insulto Pero bueno ya me lo tomo
like that no but what I was saying is that what
así no pero lo que yo estaba diciendo es
for me what
que lo que lo que para mí lo que hizo
carche auron did for me was very  ugly it was very
carche auron para mí fue muy feo fue muy
ugly I don't know what they talked about if they
feo Yo no sé en qué habran hablado si le
fixed it or not but for me it was
habrán arreglado o no pero para mí fue
very ugly it was very ugly I don't know how
muy feo fue muy feo Yo no sé como
someone didn't advise karches the guy
alguien no le aconsejó a karches el tío
[ __ ] if you want to retire from auron
[__] si te quieres retirar de auron
retire Look I almost see Juan Guarnizo's thing better
retírate Mira casi que veo mejor lo de
than Carche's because
Juan guarnizo que lo de carche porque
Juan Guarnizo in the end what he did was
Juan guarnizo al final lo que hizo fue
not want to take a position because maybe
no querer posicionarse porque a lo mejor
on one side or the other it affected him but the thing is
en un lado o en otro le afectaba pero es
that Carch took a position hate this guy is
que carch se posicionó hate este tipo es
hate imagine being a p who betrayed
de hate imagínate ser un p que traicionó
wait no I'm not going to read it I'm already coming
espera no no lo voy a leer yo ya vengo
without a filter I'm going to talk about everything
sin filtro voy a hablar de todo
imagine being a p who betrayed you his
imagínate ser un p que te tracion sus
friends because he asked him to teico kid
amigos porque se lo pidió teico chaval
happiness c it's noticeable that you're worth it barely
felidad c se nota que te vailla ap penas
200 views and so champion Look slayer you know
200 vios y así campeón Mira slayer sabes
what the good thing about everything is that when I
queé es lo bueno de todo que yo cuando
get to the end of the month I don't have to
llego a fin de mes no me tengo que
worry about whether I have enough food to make it to my
preocupar de si me llega la comida a la
mouth ask your mother the same thing [ __ ]
boca pregúntale lo mismo a tu madre [__]
subnormal eh first of all that
subnormal eh lo primero de todo eso lo
secondly I speak about whatever the balls come out of my
segundo yo hablo de lo que me sale de
balls and what I believe is
los [__] Y de lo que creo que es
right and honest At the end of the day I
correcto y honesto Yo al final del día
have a clear conscience with my
tengo la conciencia tranquila con mis
actions, with what I have done in my life, with
actos con lo que he hecho en mi vida con
what I do in my life and so on and
lo que hago en mi vida y demás e y
thirdly if there is something that I am
tercero si hay algo en lo que estoy
uneasy about or something that I am not
intranquilo o algo en lo que no estoy
happy about, thank God I go to the psychologist
contento gracias a Dios voy al psicólogo
for a day now eh I tell him my
desde hace un día eh Le cuento mis
things he helps me manage them eh if I were
movidas me ayuda a gestionarlas eh yo
you I would go to the psychologist okay I was going to
que tú iría o al psicólogo vale iba a
tell you something that I usually say to
decirte una cosa que le suelo decir a
my colleagues at the bor I can't
mis compañeros en el bor no puedo
say it live because you'll [ __ ] me up
decirla en directo porque me tias en
and I'm not going to say it and that is that he says that it
e no lo voy a decir y es que dice que le
affected him in the professional field s that
afectó en el ámbito profesional s que
because of the hate my career has been
por el hate a mí mi carrera se ha visto
affected but because of the hate
se ha visto afectada pero por el hate
carche or because of who the hate comes from and let me
carche o por de quién viene el hate y me
explain It is not the same a
explico No es lo mismo un conflicto
random conflict as a conflict with someone to
aleatorio a un conflicto con alguien a
whom I owe everything in this world I
que le deb todo en este mundillo yo con
get along very well with a guy that you already
a me llego muy bien es un tio que ya lo
know that I have I  I process a love
sabéis que yo tengo yo proceso un cariño
and admiration for a,
y una admiración por a
it's clear that let's see hate or what or that
es que claro que a ver hate o que o que
the hate, let's see because many times there are
el hate a ver porque muchas veces hay
people who are hated and
gente a la que se le tiene hate y la
people take it on the internet, they take it
gente lo coge en internet se le coge
like a sack of fire to someone for and
como un saco de boeo a alguien por y se
someone is bullied because they don't like them
le hace bullying a alguien porque cae
because they cause rejection and suddenly they do
mal porque causa rechazo y de repente
n't have to do a big thing
tampoco hace falta que haga la gran cosa
for people to take a mania okay And he
para que la gente le coja Manía vale Y
has been criticized and hated on the internet
se ha criticado y odiado en internet
okay the Internet Villain but in this
vale el Villano de Internet pero en este
case it is not a hate I'm not going to tell you
caso no es un hate no te voy a decir
either that the kid deserves the whole
tampoco que el chaval se merece toda la
life that wherever he goes they fit him
vida que por donde pase le cupan
obviously not but of course he did
evidentemente no pero claro es él hizo
something that caused a lot of rejection and that
una cosa que causó mucho rechazo y que
did damage things are man what we are
hizo daño las cosas son tío que estamos
talking about let's understand each other okay
hablando a vamos a entendernos vale
let's understand each other we are talking that
vamos a entendernos estamos hablando que
Auron was being
a auron se le estaba haciendo una
accused of flirting with minors and sexing
acusación de ligar con con menores y de
sexing is not called not
hacer sexing sexing no se llama no
sexting with a minor [ __ ] and [ __ ] already
sexting con una menor [__] y ya se
started coming out about Auro in 2013 I
empezó a sacar [__] de Auro en 2013 yo
have a career on the internet because Auro
tengo una carrera en internet por Auro
has no more and I stop saying it and  of
no tiene más y yo me jao de decirlo y de
appreciating it but I boast or
agradecerlo pero me jacto o sea
probably red the line of licking his
probablemente rojo la línea de lamerle
ass okay but I also tell you who wouldn't
el culo vale pero también te digo qui no
do it if at the end of the day you work in
lo haría si al fin y al cabo trabajas de
what you want thanks to him okay he is
lo que quieres gracias a él vale es
aware and not only because of that
consciente y ya no solamente por eso
but because of the simple fact of the relationship I
sino por el simple hecho de la relación
have with him okay circumstances that
que tengo con él vale circunstancias que
multiply that it affects your statistics
multiplica que afecte a tus estadísticas
and Therefore I got to this point more
y Por ende llegué a este punto más
easily than because of the G also my
fácilmente s que por el G también mi
career has been affected
carrera se ha visto se ha visto afectada
then I try to clumsily qualify this
luego intentó matizar torpemente este
fact but 2020 you got together with the Tops
hecho pero 2020 te juntado con los Tops
not in 2020 in fact I started streaming
no en 2020 de hecho empecé a streamear
my first stream had a peak of 6000
mi primer streaming tuvo un pico de 6000
people and an average of 3000 people I didn't
personas y una media de 3000 personas no
get together with anyone because in fact I
me junté con nadie porque de hecho yo
never wanted to get together with anything and apart from that
nunca quise juntarme con nada y aparte
I was called too the Spin rp police
se me llamaba too la policía de Spin rp
and And I started alone okay I set up my
e Y yo empecé de solo vale me monté mis
roles I looked for support from my
roles me me busqué apoyo de mis
roleplay companions such as dek
compañeros de rolplay como eran dek
tarco and many gray-haired people and so on e So
tarco y mucha gente canosa y demás e Así
not me 2020 because they invite me to play
que no yo 2020 porque me inviten a jugar
an amongas It's not that  together I
un amongas No es que me junte yo he
set this up I did it alone okay
montado esto lo he hecho yo solo vale
another thing is that I was lucky
otra cosa es que haya tenido suerte de
that obviously a large
Que obviamente pues ha venido un gran
audience of people came to see a server and
Público de personas a ver un servidor y
I was roleplaying on that server but
yo estaba roleando en ese servidor pero
what is my role I set it up
lo que es mi rol me lo he montado yo
alone Okay and the people who came to see me
solito Vale y la gente que venía a verme
came to see me for my role not for anything else
me venía a ver por mi rol no por otra
Well no because [ __ ] but in a in
cosa Bueno pues no porque jod pero en un
a recognized c his what he owes to
en un c reconocido su lo que le debe a
auron and Ah now he says no I
auron y Ah ahora dice que no yo me
would love to know what it was that they talked about
encantaría saber qué es lo que hablaron
privately and terms were left It's that
por privado y términos quedaron Es que
auron got very lukewarm uncle auron took
auron se puso muy tibio tío auron tomó
a stance of saying look let this be
una postura de decir mira que esto se
forgotten you know outside I apologize if I have
olvide sabes fuera me disculpo si lo he
done it and if I haven't done it I also
hecho y si no lo he hecho también me
apologize just in case okay there is a
disculpo por si acaso vale que hay un
misconception about how I started on
concepto equivocado de como yo empecé en
Twitch that I see that is not entirely clear
Twitch que veo que no no está claro del
okay not worth it I set up my roleplay rp by myself
todo vale no vale Yo mi rolplay rp me lo
okay without
monté yo solo de acuerdo sin ayuda de
anyone's help I set it up by myself I just went and
nadie me lo monté yo solo yo cogí y le
told my
dije a mi
mother no I don't know go I swear I don't
madre no no lo sé iá te lo juro que no
know song And from there there is  a
lo sé canción Y a partir de ahí hay un
misconception like emp on Twitch
concepto equivocado como emp en Twitch
that is not reality at least at that time it
que no realidad por lo menos en aquel
was in the end things as they
era la que era en el cabo las cosas como
are I have a career on the internet but
son yo tengo una carrera en internet
now you can tap yourself
poro ya te puedes dar todos los
in the chest all you want saying
golpecitos que quieras en el pechito de
I did this or I did that okay I mean
Yo hice esto o yo Hice aquello vale o
you can't ask a
sea tú no puedes pedirle tampoco a una
person to put their ass out for I don't know
persona que ponga el culo durante no sé
how long and stay quiet with the
cuánto tiempo y se quede callado con el
hate because that's the best solution you know you know
hate porque es la mejor solución sabes
that no you can't ask
sees que no tampoco se lo puedes pedir a
a person either there are people who
una persona hay gente a la que sí que lo
can take it and say I ignore it I ignore it I
puede [__] y decir lo ignoro lo ignoro
ignore it and when I completely ignore it it
lo ignoro y cuando lo ignoro del todo ya
disappears and that's it the
desaparece y ya está ha pasado el
Temporal has passed and that's it Yeah poo very vague of course
Temporal y ya está Sí poo muy vaga clar
ignore it and that's it ignore it depends
ignóralo y ya está ignóralo depende que
on what context it is in not all
sea en qué contexto no todos los
streamers earn a million euros a year
streamers ganan al año un millón de
and you millions of gentlemen people
euros y ti millones de señores gente la
who
que
ca50 turkeys up you know that many
ca50 pavos hast arriba sabes que muchas
times Elio justifies himself as saying no
veces se justifica Elio como diciendo no
you're too famous [ __ ] you're too little famous
t mu famoso jod de mu poco famoso
also I mean the Face and such does not understand
también o sea el Face y tal no entiende
economic issues or
de cuestiones económicas ni de
Followers  So I think that for someone who is
Seguidores Así que creo que al que es
very famous it is easier to hit someone who
muy famoso es más fácil pegar un palo
takes for granted but who has been
que das por hecho que te pero que que
received by everyone. He also spoke about the
recibido por todos l también habló de la
durability of the negative labels
durabilidad de las etiquetas negativas
that are placed on you on the internet specifically
que te ponen en internet concretamente
towards him for this mythical story that
hacia él por esta historia que publicó
aurono published and what trab perro says
aurono mítica y lo que dice trab perro
is also true, I mean, the jokes do not
también es verdad o sea las funas No
expire if there has been one of you, no, they do not
caducan si tú ha habido una no que no
expire but if there has been a very big one
caduquen pero si ha habido una muy gorda
related to a person, anything that has
relacionada con una persona a nada que
been a little bit bigger has already run out
haya sido un poquito más gorda ya se ha
of imen, that's already been in a
quedado sin imen esaa ya seado en un
casual public and when And when for
público casual y cuando Y cuando por
example you later give an opinion on
ejemplo tú después das una opinión de
something, they are always going to end up throwing you out, you
algo siempre te van a acabar tirando
know, it's like you're condemned to, I don't
sabes es como que estás como condenado a
know, I have to one day in a
yo que sé tengo quear un día en un
streaming you come and punch me twice you
streaming vienes y me pegas dos
tell me if you are a fat son
puñetazos me dices si eres un gordo hijo
of a [ __ ] and I do little by little and it goes
de [__] y yo me poco a una y se te
viral from there on what you
viraliza de a partir de allas lo que
do is like always Ah but this
hagas est es como siempre Ah pero este
was the one that I don't know what but and only and
fue el que no sé qué pero y solamente y
many times there is only one way for that to
muchas veces solamente hay una manera de
happen is if there are several
que eso de que eso pase es si hay varias
people involved that those people
personas involucradas que esas personas
all agree to say this
se pongan todas de acuerdo en decir esto
is not the case and insist and say this is not the
no es así y insistir y decir esto no es
case until that narrative is removed,
así hasta que se quite esa narrativa yo
for example, my thing, the rat thing,
por ejemplo lo mío lo de la rata Yo
until Auron tomorrow
hasta que auron el día de mañana no
comes out saying live, Hey guys, hey, you
salga diciendo en directo Oye chavales
call this guy a rat, this guy
eh le llamáis rata a este tío este tío
is nothing like this, until Auron feels
no es nada de esto hasta que auron no le
like doing that, I'm going to continue with
de la gana hacer eso yo voy a seguir con
that image my whole [ __ ] life, my whole life for the
esa imagen toda la [__] vida Toda la
casual public, my whole life,
vida para el público casual toda la vida
it's like that, it's also very noticeable on
es así que también eso se nota mucho en
TikTok and on other platforms that it's
tiktok y en otras plataformas que que es
like, Oh, but this was the one with, I don't know what it is, that
como Ah pero este era el de no sé qué es
happens a lot, that's going to stay, that's going to stay like that my
eso pasa much eso se va a quedar eso se
whole life unless
queda así toda la vida a no ser que la
people agree to say, Hey,
gente se ponga de acuerdo en decir Oye
let's stop this [ __ ] nonsense, but it's
vamos a parar esta [__] tontería pero es
very difficult for that type of
muy difícil que ese tipo de ese tipo de
thing to happen, I mean, it's very difficult for it to
cosas o sea es muy difícil que pueda
reach the end because people
llegar para al final porque a la gente
always love to be able to, yes, on
le encanta siempre poder s nosotros en
a much more different scale, it
una escala muchísimo más diferente nos
happens to us with, yes, it's a request, Indira to
pasa con sí es una petición Indira a
Oron, Play, yes, you know, just from one sentence
oron Play sía m sabes solo por una frase
specific of the sports project that they
concreta del proyecto deportivo que
pull on that all their [ __ ] life Well well well
tiran de eso toda la [__] vida Bueno
Apparently carche is not
bueno bueno Al parecer a carche no le
worth gestures like this daur Play the other
valen gestos como este daur Play el otro
day because the guy sh left Because he
día porque se ha ido el tío sh Porque se
went to kiik I read it on Twitter because
ha ido a kiik lo leí en Twitter porque
the person stole from me asking for forgiveness I
la persona me ar robó pidiendo perdón O
mean the truth is I was freaking out but I
sea que la verdad me quedé flipando pero
thought it was a super nice gesture do you
me pareció un gesto superbonito os
remember the other day live when
acordáis el otro día en directo cuando
I took the account of a person who had
cogí una cuenta de una persona que hab
come in to say [ __ ] in the chat he
ha entrado a decir [__] al chat me ha
wrote me on Twitter to say that he had
escrito por Twitter para decir que le
also been banned from the auron chat
han baneado también del chat de auron
for having made that
por haber soltado ese comentario de
shitty comment and that he apologizes I mean it
[__] y que pide disculpas O sea me
seemed to me a very nice gesture on the part of
pareció un gesto muy bonito por parte de
auron and the auron moderators the
auron y de los moderadores de auron la
truth is sincerely I thought it was a
verdad sinceramente me pareció un gesto
nice gesture the truth is the baby needs a
bonito la verdad el bebé necesita una
public rectification until well
rectificación pública hasta que bueno
auron has had more nice gestures with
auron ha tenido más gestos bonitos con
him imagine The goal first auron then
él imagina El tanto primero auron luego
Abi e has no talent to get his
Abi e no tiene talento para levantarse
own audience up and he would dress up as a
un público propio yo él me vestía de
rat in a live and stop making those
rata en un directo y ya no hagas esos
comments please eh can you give your opinion
comentarios por favor eh podéis opinar
no disrespect okay Don't say
sin faltar al respeto vale No digáis
those things man let's see, well in all
esas cosas tío a ver yo bueno en honor a
honesty I would have been part of it no disrespect
la verdad fuera parte sin faltar respeto
but I would have done it because
pero yo sí que lo hubiera hecho porque
I Cache deo even my shadow you
yo me Cacho deo hasta de mi sombra me
understand me Yes yes yes me if people don't
entiendes Yo sí sí sí yo si la gente no
stop calling me a rat I've seen myself as a
me para de llamar rata me he visto de
rat But well I understand that if he doesn't
rata Pero bueno entiendo que si no se
feel good what are you sending me in the
siente bien qué me estáis mandando en el
group you [ __ ] Auro tomorrow he's
grupo cabrones Auro en el día de mañana
not going to go out saying it live and kids
no sal va diciendo en directo e chavales
eh you call this guy a rat this guy
eh le llamáis rata a este tío este tío
is nothing like this until Auron feels like
no es nada de esto hasta que auron no le
doing that I'm going to continue with
de la gana hacer eso yo voy a seguir con
that image my whole [ __ ] life My whole
esa imagen toda la [__] vida Toda la
life for the casual public my whole life let's
vida para el público casual toda la vida
see well It's true that Auron never
a ver bien Es cierto que auron nunca lo
mentioned it directly I've even seen how
mencionó directa incluso he visto como
coworkers or ex-colleagues
compañeros de trabajo o excompañeros se
joined in this ball of hate This goes for
sumaban a esta bola de odio Esto va por
This goes for carche Win michu that Felipe
Esto va por carche Win michu que Felipe
Felipe I don't think he took it that much into
Felipe yo no creo que lo tuviera tan en
account Felipe 360 this you know what I'm
cuenta Felipe 360 este sabes lo que te
telling you and but yes the thing is that Win
digo e pero sí que lo de es que Win
michu did a lot to make it  viralize
michu hizo mucho para que se viralizar
some things it seems that he was
algunas cosas parece que estaba como
waiting to take advantage of that moment you know to
esperando a aprovechar ese momento sabes
throw at Auron and Sara
para para tirarle a auron y a Sara
Because well because they had made
Porque bueno porque habían hecho las
peace with Dallas simply to
pases con Dallas simplemente para
make it more and more Vegeta was never very
hacerla más y más Vegeta nunca quedó muy
clear eh the Vegeta thing was not very clear
claro eh lo de Vegeta no quedó muy claro
but apart from that it is that apart who
pero aparte de eso es que aparte quién
else dude Because the Juan Guarnizo thing I
más tío Porque lo de Juan guarnizo yo
understand that maybe
entiendo que a lo mejor se eche de menos
a positioning is missed but neither, I mean
un posicionamiento pero tampoco o sea
Juan did not arrive Juan did not even arrive
Juan no llegó Juan no llegó ni siquiera
to insinuate no but very lukewarm Auron eh
a insinuar no pero muy tibio el auron eh
And bigger in the mythical history Auron also does
Y más grande en la mítica historia auron
not mention anyone about dressing up
tampoco menciona a nadie lo de vestirse
as a rat is to joke and that's it but
de rata es para bromear y ya pero
behave well Yes, he did mention Carche, his
pórtate bien Sí que mencionó a carche su
keche was the most notorious on a
queche fue el más notorio a nivel
public level Because I do tell you there are
público Porque yo sí que os digo es hay
things that fall by their own weight
cosas que cais por su propio peso
then deserved or not deserved to be
entonces merecido o no merecido que te
called a traitor Anyway, Carche already
llamen traidor De todas formas carche ya
stated that he had resolved things
manifestó que había solventado las cosas
with Auronplay apart from that he called everyone who
con auronplay aparte llamó payaso a todo
called him a traitor a clown and you have
aquel que le llamaba traidor y os habéis
stopped getting carried away much by him here it was a
dejado de llevar mucho por el aquí era
lie okay here  He had
mentira vale aquí Él sí que había
sent like an audio or something like that I don't
mandado como un audio o algo así no me
remember exactly what happened
acuerdo exactamente qué es lo que pasó
but it was a lie I mean no they weren't
pero era mentira O sea no no estaban
okay He wanted to understand here that
bien Él quiso aquí a entender que los
channels like mine invented the
canales como el mío nos inventamos la
funa towards him never a kiss bu well and I'm
funa hacia él jamá un beso bu bueno y se
telling this to everyone who has
lo digo a todo el [__] mundo que me ha
called me r and so on and I'm going to tell you do
llamado r y demás y os voy a decir
you know why Because I have spoken with
sabéis por qué Porque yo he hablado con
abron in private and there is no
abrón por privado y no hay ningún
problem with him nor has he taken anything I have
problema con ni se lo ha tomado mal nada
said badly because there is nothing to
de lo que he dicho por qué no hay nada
take badly because there is nothing to
que tomárselo mal que no hay nada que
take badly from what I have said I am not
tomárselo mal lo que yo he dicho yo no
going to ask or demand that people
voy a pedir ni exigir que me de la gente
apologize to me for that the people who have
disculpas de eso la gente que me ha
called me Rat and all that because I don't want
llamado Rata y todo eso porque no quiero
the apologies from those people I don't feel
las disculpas de esa gente no me vce la
sorry for them The only thing I can say is to
pena Yo lo único que puedo decir es a
all the people who have been accusing me
toda la gente que me estado acusando
these days of being disloyal False Friend
estos días por desleal Falso Amigo
when literally I have spoken with
cuando literalmente yo he hablado con
auron in private and there is no
auron por privado y no hay ningún
problem Between him and I please invite
problema Entre él y yo por favor invita
Fran cuesta suba please Well look
a Fran cuesta suba por favor Pues mira
Andrea Frank right now Fran is live
Andrea Frank ahora mismo Está en directo
now  same It's live eh I do
Fran ahora mismo Está en directo eh
n't know if it's for members But look the
no s si es para miembro Pero mira la
burger was expensive a kiss my
hamburguesa le salió cara un beso mis
Landy the burger didn't sit well with
Landy la hamburguesa no le sentó bien
everyone that day for Look over there it is
ese día a todo el mundo por Mira por ahí
Look at the lake Look at the
está Mira el lago Mira cabr
revolutionized kids calm down there's
revolucionadas tranquilos ahí tienes a
Fran in case you want to come in look here it was the
Fran por si quieres entrar mira aquí fue
doggy style This is the camera that
lo de perrito Esta es la cámara que le
catches him doggy style okay Okay today I
pilla lo de perrito vale Bueno hoy he
uploaded a video today I uploaded a video
subid un vídeo hoy he subid un vídeo
but I don't need to
pero a Fran no hace falta que yo lo
invite Fran Fran uploads whenever he feels like it Fran uploads
invite Fran sube cuando le da la gana
whenever he feels like it Andrea
Fran sube cuando le da la gana Andrea
Today she uploads a video on the main page with
Hoy sube un vídeo en el principal con
Fran Have you seen it today I uploaded a video
Fran Lo habéis visto hoy subí un vídeo
wait I'm going to promote it here because there are
espera lo voy a promocionar aquí que hay
many times there are many times that we
muchas veces que hay muchas veces que
upload so much that you miss
subimos tanto tenido no que se os queda
some behind
alguno por detrás
you here you have it Look okay you okay look at it I mean it
ti aquí lo tenéis Mira vale ti vale
's a
miradlo o sea es un
little bit I had to cut and
poquito he tenido que recortar y que
put a little more like okay it's a piece
poner un poco más like vale es un trozo
of live that I had to delete the other
de directo que tuve que eliminar el otro
day because Fran gets carried away he gets
día porque Fran se embala se embala se
carried away But well I did rescue this piece
embala Pero bueno este trozo sí que lo
because it's controversial okay in case you
rescaté porque es polémico vale por si
want to see it We remain the same  The only thing I
lo queréis ver Seguimos igual lo único
can tell you is that We're still the same he
que os puedo decir es que Seguimos igual
says Really if you stopped following me
dice De verdad si me dejaste de seguir
because you followed me don't follow me anymore I do
porque me seguías no me sigas nunca más
n't want you here that's what it is ha no
no te quiero por aquí es lo que ha no
better No no no more seriously that's it
tiene más vale No no tiene más en serio
Aha you've come off as clowns you
ya está Aha habéis quedado como payasos
've let yourself be carried away by hate
os habéis dejado llevar por el odio
you've come off as p trying to put
habéis quedado como p intentado meter en
a person in your head I don't want on this
la cabeza una persona no quiero en este
channel literally they took it They left you with
canal literal lo tomaron Te dejaron
low viewers eh Let's see this
bajitos de espectadores eh A ver esto
to start with is a lie We're still the same I
para empezar es mentira Seguimos igual
say this more than anything because you didn't come back I had
lo digo más que nada porque no volviste
thought exactly that when
a había pensado justamente eso cuando lo
I heard it I mean it's a lie it's
he escuchado o sea es mentira es mentira
literally a lie that everything remained the same
literalmente que todo siguiera igual
but let's go publicly it has been seen
pero vamos públicamente se ha visto
collaborating with him Oh and yes
colaborar con él Ah y si también están
things are also like that Until Auro
las cosas Hasta que Auro en el día de
tomorrow no kids you call
mañana no e chavales le llamáis rata a
this guy a rat he's not any of this until
este tío no es nada de esto hasta que
now he doesn't feel like doing that I'm going to
ahora no le dé la gana hacer eso yo voy
continue with that image my whole [ __ ]
a seguir con esa imagen toda la [__]
life All my life for the casual public
vida Toda la vida para el público casual
all my life what does it cost him to do you this
toda la vida qué le cuesta hacerte este
favor No friend let's move forward because they
favor No amiguito avancemos porque
were trivializing people  that
estuvieron banalizando a la gente que
throws hate More than anything
tira hate Más que nada porque que nada
because it's simply looking for interaction it doesn't
porque simplemente Busca interacción no
depend on when it's your turn when it's your
depende de cuando te toque cuando te
turn boom come on [ __ ] I'm going to give
toque pum venga [__] voy a darle un
this guy a stick I give him a stick I'm going
palito a este le doy un palo me voy
viral with the stick and I say damn How cool is it to
viral con el palo y digo [__] Cómo Mola
give sticks sticks I believe the vast majority of those who
dar palos palos yo creo la gran mayoría
make a viral tweet crawling to
que que hacen un tweet viral gateando a
someone it's precisely because they want to
alguien es precisamente porque quieren
be viral I mean I don't even think they have
ser viral O sea yo no creo ni que tengan
anything personal against you or sometimes they
nada personal en contra de ti o a veces
do but I think that viralization is a
sí pero creo que la viralización es un
great point of creating the tweet like The
gran punto de crear el tweet como El
Alchemist Belce perfect for the greatest
alquimista belce perfecto para la mayor
possible viralization is it is I have the
viralización posible es es yo tengo la
theory that it's impossible for you to
teoría de que es imposible de que tú
put a tweet against a person
pongas un tweet en contra de una persona
and for it to be something personal I have the
y que sea algo personal yo tengo la
theory that you have to put it
teoría de que tú lo tienes que poner
because you know that est I think it's
porque sabes que est yo creo que es un
2% of people who take it as something
2% de la gente la que lo tenga como algo
personal because you're lying down In my
personal porque estás tumbado En mi
opinion if you take something from the world of
opinión si te tomas algo del mundo del
streaming to the personal it has to be
streaming al lo personal tiene que ser
something very specific to you you know I know that
algo muy específico tuyo sabes yo que sé
any news has come out
de ha salido cualquier noticia
related to something that affects you
relacionado con algo que te toca de
firsthand and then it does become
primera mano y entonces sí se convierte
something personal and in the end it's what
en algo personal y y al final es lo que
you  you say they stick with those
tú dices que se quedan con esas
narratives that no matter what I do, no,
narrativas de que haga lo que haga no
but you said what if I don't even say it.
pero tú dijiste que tal si no lo dice ni
Well then you're screwed, and even more so on
yo Bueno pues te jodes y más en redes
social networks like tiktok. The vast majority, and
sociales como tiktok J la gran mayoría y
with the vast majority who are commenting
con la gran mayoría que está comentando
all day on tiktok and commenting, the plan is very
todo el día tiktok y comenta plan es muy
short, a tiktok to comment, lamentably, to
cortos un tiktok a comentar lamente a
insult, it is very short, I'm
insultar es muy corto tiempo lo siento
very sorry, definitive, given this analysis, there
mucho definitiva dado este análisis no
is no greater reason to
es mayor motivo todavía para no hacerle
ignore these clowns carch, curious this
caso a estos payasos carch curioso este
Take, the truth is curious this Take, curious
Take la verdad curioso este Take curioso
this Take, it still hurts me badly from
este Take me sigue doliendo mals lo de
watching Formula 1, I think I weigh
ver la Fórmula 1 creo que yo peso ahora
80 kg right now, I think I'm 73, betray or
mismo 80 kg creo que yo 73 traicionar o
Play, calm down, if you want, I'll put it in, don't
Play tranquilo si quieres la meto no te
[ __ ] with me, ragi, wait. Let's run into her for a
jodes ragi espérate Vamos a toparla un
moment. Oh, I'm writing it in
momento Ay lo estoy escribiendo en
green, very perfect, wonderful. Oh, yes,
verde bien perfecto maravilloso Ah sí
what did you think I was going to write to him and
qué pensabas que le iba a escribir y que
give you a video? No, friend, no, no, no.
te iba a dar un vídeo no amigo no no no
Calm down, I know you're going to try to get it out, no,
Cálmate sé que vas a intentar sacarlo no
calm down. It's role Player, no, I haven't
calma Es es role Player no s no he
even been able to write it. Besides, you don't speak
podido ni escribirlo Aparte tú no hablas
German, don't put everything in Google Translate.  They
alemán no metas en el traductor Google
tell you and that's it, but what does my
todo lo que te dicen y ya está pero y mi
audience think about this? Well, look, there's
público que opin de esto Pues mira hay
a problem, there's a problem, eh, how do I
una movida hay una movida eh cómo lo
look for it on Karime's Twitter? There's no
busco en el Twitter de Karime no hay una
problem,
movida lo ha borrado
Karime deleted it. Yes, look here, the ladies are fighting. Let's see if we don't
Karime Sí mira aquí peleándose las
lose the thread,
ver si vamos a ver si no pierdo el hilo
okay, let's see if I don't lose the thread.
vale vamos a ver si no pierdo el hilo
[Music]
[Música]